

PROFILE

Android developer with 8 years of experience. Worked in both, small and large distributed teams, that counted more than 100 developers from different countries.

Tech stack: Android SDK, Kotlin, Java, Jetpack Compose, Dagger/Hilt, Junit, Retrofit, GraphQL, Protobuff, Blaze, Critique, Fig, Git, EventBus, Glide, Lokalise, Postman, Jira, Figma, Slack, Mattermost, BlueJeans React Native, Expo, Redux

CONTACT

LinkedIn
https://www.linkedin.com/in/boja
n-pavlovic86/

EMAIL: pavlovicboki@yahoo.com

PHONE: +381 62 617 146

BOJAN PAVLOVIC

Android developer 8 years of experience in industry

EDUCATION

Faculty of Electronic Engineering, Nis, Serbia 2005 - present Software engineer – Department for computer science

High school "Milentije Popovic", Pirot, Serbia 2001 - 2005

WORK EXPERIENCE

SyncIt Group - Android developer September 2015 - December 2016

BAD Sistems – Android developer February 2017 – August 2018

Ates Soft – Android developer September 2018 – September 2019

Borne Agency – Android developer February 2020 – July 2020

Ates Soft – Android developer January 2021 – November 2021

Grid Dynamics – Android developer February 2022 – January 2023

PROJECTS

I'm Here – App for automatic sending of SMS. User draws geofence on map, around desired object, and when app detects entering inside that geofence, SMS with custom defined text is automatically sent to previously selected number.

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.syncitgroup.android.iamhere

Smart House – Purpose of project was developing app for controlling various electronic devices like LED lights, electronic locks, house windows etc... OpenHub is used as a middleware between app and electronic devices.

BeRemasi – Project for client from cleaning industry. Purpose of app is to track time spent on work and travel by cleaners.

BadCan – App used for syncing files from phone to cloud account. Rebranding NextCloud app.

Kanbansi – Management app intended for use on tablets. Similar to Trello app. User (based on his role) can create, delete, edit projects, add new cards, descriptions to cards, or add files to project. Used for project progress tracking, based on Kanban methodology.

Koridor10 – App for measuring average speed of car on a Serbian highway. When app is started, automatically starts/ends current average speed calculation when user passes through pay toll.

DSAP - Digital Shopper Activation Platform – Multi modular framework for creating loyalty apps.

Heineken Biertegoed – Loyalty app for Heineken H0 (non-alcoholic) beer campaign. Users can scan receipts, manually enter codes, or send/receive points from friends. After some point level is reached, user can redeem beer or other present at the bar.

Kanzi – Loyalty app for apple seller client. Enables collecting codes and getting discounts.

Dekamarkt Smaakmakers – Loyalty app for the Dekamarkt supply chain. Users can get prizes and various discounts.

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=nl.dekamarkt.smaakmakers

Pathe All Stars – Loyalty app for the Pathe cinema chain. Users can get various discounts and promotions. https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=nl.pathe.allstars

Knauf Extra – loyalty app for the client from construction industry.

Mona - Loyalty app for the Friesland Campina product.

USD – Urban Self Defence – app for learning self-defence by watching courses.

Jobu – App for client from sports industry. Two types of users: those who teach and those who are signing up for courses.

Enables teaching/scheduling various courses like yoga, dance, boxing, gym etc...

[Undisclosed name] - eBanking application for large bank client. Purpose is to offer even more services through app that other traditional banks. One app for multiple markets.

[Undisclosed name] - app for well-known client from sports industry. Implementing new features.

[Undisclosed name] – app for a client from FAANG group. Adding analytics features.